daoq.cn 2014-09-08

# Memay Enterprise | Rhinestone, transfer motifs, garment accessaries, Crystal Beads, Sequines and Spangle trimmings.

Your Site Now: : Home>>About MeMay>>Company Brief 

Memay.com knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting memay.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

### Personal Information About Customers

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at memay.com. Here are the types of information we gather.

### Information You Give Us

We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.

You provide most information when you search, buy, participate in questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire; select items for a Scrapbook. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and phone number; and financial information.

### Automatic Information

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses memay.com.

Other examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click stream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart and Scrapbook between visits.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browser will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. In addition, a number of companies offer utilities designed to help you visit Web sites anonymously.

Although we will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience at memay.com if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these tools exist. Keep in mind that cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of memay.com most useful features, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

### E-mail Communications

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from memay.com if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please notify us by using one of the options below under How to Access Your Information.

### Information from Other Sources

For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

Sharing of Personal Information Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. Therefore, we do not share any of the personally identifiable information that we receive. We use it solely to better serve our clientele by bringing the most popular items where they are the easiest to locate and in connection with other promotional tools.

Demographic and profile data may be collected at our Web site. We may use this data to tailor the user's experience at our Web site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences and to otherwise optimize our Web site so that it is more beneficial to users like yourself and to us.

The demographic information may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. Aggregate basis means that your information will be generalized with the data we collect from all our users. For example, we may share the average age or income level of our user’s with advertisers. We will not share personally identifiable information, such as contact information, unique identifiers, financial information and demographic information, with advertisers about any particular individual who uses our Web site.

How to Access Your Information you can access your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by phoning (212-204-9595), via e-mail ([info@memay.com](mailto:info@memay.com)). We use this procedure to safeguard your information. To protect your privacy and security, we will take all reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. You can correct factual errors in personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly show the error.

### Security of Personal Information

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.

We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

Links to Other Sites This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions If you choose to visit memay.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of China. If you have any concern about privacy at memay.com, please send us a thorough description to [info@memay.com](mailto:info@memay.com), and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
